Viewers all over the world, what God is about to do in your life -
hear from the Prophet:
I shall say that which I shall live to see happen!
Hear what God is about to do at this moment.
Are you ready to hear?
Yes.
I'm not praying for you; rather I'm telling you the will of God.
You will pray; I will tell you the will of God.
I will guide you.
Because prayer has language.
If you don’t speak the language, you are saying words.
But when you speak the language, you are praying prayer.
Tell your neighbour, "Prayer has language".
Prayer has language
If you don’t speak the language, you are saying words.
But when you speak the language, you are praying prayer.
Hallelujah.
Amen.
Wave you hands.
What is your situation?
I command you to be free, in the name of Jesus!
Are you being demonized?
Are you not sure of yourself?
Are you facing generational curses, limitation in progress, hardship, poverty?
I command you to be released, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips!
I said, "I command you to be released, in the name of Jesus!"
Open your lips and begin to say your situation.
Begin to speak out!
What are you facing?
What is your situation?
Your situation could be poverty, hardship, marital problems.
Are you demonized?
Are you sick?
Are you possessed by demons?
In the name of Jesus Christ!
What is your situation?
I want you to mention your situation and say, enough is enough to that situation!
Say, "Enough is enough to that hardship!
Enough is enough to that sickness!
Enough is enough to that hardship!
Enough is enough, in the name of Jesus!"
Say, "Enough is enough!"
Enough is enough!
Open your lips and begin to rebuke it in the name of Jesus!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Say after me, "Hardship – I face them no more!"
Begin to insert you situation there.
Whatever situation you are facing - sickness - I face them no more, in the name of Jesus!
Limitations in progress – I face them no more!
In the name of Jesus!
Marital problems – I face them no more!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Say these words after me:
"Be thou loosed, bondage in my life!"
Prayer!
Be thou loosed, bondage in my life!
Hardship, limitation in progress, sickness and disease, disappointment - be thou loosed, in the name of Jesus!
Open your lips!
Say, "Be thou loosed, bondage in my life!
Sickness, limitation in progress, disappointment – be thou loosed!
In the name of Jesus!"
Begin to loose them!
Open your lips and begin...
It is the will of God to loose them at this moment!
It is the will of God to do so at this moment!
Begin to loose them!
Loose them!
It is His will to do so at this moment!
It is His will to do so!
The end has come to that affliction!
The end has come to that infirmity!
The end has come to that situation in your life!
The end has come!
Begin to loose them!
Loose them!
Loose them in the name of Jesus!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, agree with me; it is God's will to free you!
It is God's will to release you!
It is His will to heal you!
It is His will to deliver you!
It is His will to bless you!
It is His will!
Agree with me.
Say, "it is God's will".
It is God's will
to free me at this moment!
It is God's will to free me!
It is His will at this moment to free me!
Poverty in your life,
affliction in your life,
infirmity in your life,
limitation in progress,
marital problem, be thou loosed!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, the end has come to that affliction.
The end has come to that bondage.
Anything that has a beginning must have an end.
Tell your situation, "the end has come; I face them no more.
Disappointments – I face them no more!
Afflictions – I face them no more!
Limitations in progress – I face them no more!
I face them no more!
Viewers all over the world, you are with us; we are with you.
As surely as the Lord lives, the end has come to that affliction, to that sickness and disease,
to that infirmity, to that limitation in progress.
As surely as the Lord lives, you face them no more.
You face them no more!
In the name of Jesus!
Let the weak say, "I'm strong!"
Let the poor say, "I'm blessed!"
Let the sick say, "I'm healed!"
In Jesus Christ's name.
Rejoice!
Anything that has a beginning must have an end.
The end has come!
I can't hear you!
Say, "I face them no more!"
I face them no more!
I can't hear you!
Affliction.
Sickness!
Infirmity!
Limitation in progress!
Disappointment!
Marital problems!
Poverty!
Hardship!
I face them no more, in the name of Jesus!
I face them no more.
Speak to yourself.
Speak to yourself this time.
Begin to speak to yourself!
I face them no more!
That trouble – I face them no more!
That sickness – I face them no more!
That unpleasant situation – I face them no more!
Demonic activity – I face them no more!
Open your lips in the name of Jesus!
Speak to yourself!
You know your situation!
Begin to mention your situation!
Say after me, "I face them no more!"
I face them no more!
Yes.
You hardship, poverty, disappointment, marital problem, sickness and disease, limitation in progress -
I face them no more!
Open your lips, speak!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I shall prophesy that which I shall live to see accomplished!
Rejoice!
Let the weak say, "I am strong".
Let the poor say, "I am blessed".
Let the sick say, "I am healed".
I'm delivered.
I'm free.
I'm blessed!
Rejoice!
Rejoice, begin to rejoice.
Praise is rising eyes are turning to You
Put your hands together.
We turn to You
Hope is stirring hearts are longing for You
We long for You
When we see You
We find strength to face the day
In Your presence
All our tears are washed away
When we see You
We find strength to face the day
In Your presence
All our tears are washed away
Hosanna
You are the God who saves us
Worthy of all our praises
Hosanna
Come have Your way among us
We welcome You here Lord Jesus
Put your hands together.
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
The best is yet to come
Always
Everybody
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
As we continue to relax
In Your precious arms
Holy Ghost
The best is yet to come
Always
Blessed be the name of the Lord
Most high
Hallelujah
Blessed be the name of the Lord
Most high
Hallelujah
Blessed be the name of the Lord
Most high
Now listen
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
And you really wanna show it
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
Clap your hands
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
And you really wanna show it
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
Lift up your hands
If you're happy and you know it
Jump up
To the sky
If you're happy and you know it
And you really wanna show it
Jump up
Come on
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
And you really wanna show it
If you're happy and you know it
Say Amen
Shout Emmanuel
If you're happy and you know it
And you really wanna show it
Shout Emmanuel
If you're happy and you know it
Clap your hands
Now listen
If you're happy and you know it
Sit down
And you really wanna show it
If you're happy and you know it
Sit down
Jump up
If you're happy and you know it
And you really wanna show it
Jump up
Oh when the saints go marching in
Oh Lord I want to be in that number
I'm going to march to Heaven one day
This way
Oh when the saints go marching in
Oh Lord I want to be in that number
Oh when the sun will shine no more
Oh when the saints go marching in
I'm going to march to Heaven one day
Hallelujah
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.